- ObjectiveID: 9401_MountVector
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9401_MountVector_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9401_Horse
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9401_MountVector_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock && !9401_Befriend_Started
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9401_MountVector_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_MountVector_title"
  Description: "@9401_MountVector_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_MountVector_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_MountVector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_MountVector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_MountVector_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9401_BefriendHorse
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9401_Befriend_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9401_Horse
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: MountType_Unlock_Horse
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9401_BefriendHorse_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_BefriendHorse_title"
  Description: "@9401_BefriendHorse_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_BefriendHorse_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_BefriendHorse_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_BefriendHorse_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_BefriendHorse_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9401_TutorialFood
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9401_TutorialFood_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9401_Horse
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9401_TutorialComplete
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9401_Tutorial_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@9401_TutorialFood_title"
  Description: "@9401_TutorialFood_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_TutorialFood_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_TutorialFood_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_TutorialFood_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_TutorialFood_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9401_VectorWF
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9401_VectorWF_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9402_Conman
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9401_VectorWF_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9401_VectorWF_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_VectorWF_title"
  Description: "@9401_VectorWF_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_VectorWF_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_VectorWF_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_VectorWF_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_VectorWF_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9403_VectorWolves
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9403_VectorWolves_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9403_Wolf
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9403_VectorWolves_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9403_VectorWolves_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_VectorWolves_title"
  Description: "@9403_VectorWolves_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_VectorWolves_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_VectorWolves_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9403_VectorWolves_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9403_VectorWolves_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9403_FreeWolves
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9403_FreeWolves_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9403_Wolf
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: MountType_Unlock_DireWolf
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9403_FreeWolves_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_FreeWolves_title"
  Description: "@9403_FreeWolves_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_FreeWolves_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_FreeWolves_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9403_FreeWolves_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9403_FreeWolves_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9403_VectorBS
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9403_VectorBS_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9404_Record
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9403_VectorBS_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: Expansion_2023_Unlock
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9403_VectorBS_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_VectorBS_title"
  Description: "@9403_VectorBS_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_VectorBS_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_VectorBS_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9403_VectorBS_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9403_VectorBS_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9403_VectorLions
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9403_VectorLions_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9405_Lion
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9403_VectorLions_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9403_VectorLions_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_VectorLions_title"
  Description: "@9403_VectorLions_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_VectorLions_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_VectorLions_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9403_VectorLions_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9403_VectorLions_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9405_RescueLion
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 9405_RescueLion_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9405_Lion
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: MountType_Unlock_Sabretooth
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_VectorLions_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 1.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 9405_RescueLion_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_RescueLion_title"
  Description: "@9405_RescueLion_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9405_RescueLion_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_RescueLion_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9405_RescueLion_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9405_RescueLion_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EF_Tour_0
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: 9401_FirstRace_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9401_Horse
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EF_Tour_0_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: MountType_Unlock_Horse
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EF_Tour_0_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Tour_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_FirstRace_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_FirstRace_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_FirstRace_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_FirstRace_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EF_Rally_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EF_Rally_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EF_Rally_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EF_Rally_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Rally_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Rally_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EF_Rally_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EF_Rally_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EF_Rally_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EF_Rally_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Rally_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Rally_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EF_Tour_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EF_Tour_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EF_Tour_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EF_Tour_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Tour_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EF_Tour_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EF_Tour_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EF_Tour_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EF_Tour_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Tour_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EF_Tour_3
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EF_Tour_3_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EF_Tour_3_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EF_Tour_3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Tour_3_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_3_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: WF_Rally_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: WF_Rally_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: WF_Rally_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: WF_Rally_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9402_Rally_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9402_Rally_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: WF_Rally_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: WF_Rally_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: WF_Rally_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: WF_Rally_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9402_Rally_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9402_Rally_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: WF_Tour_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: WF_Tour_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: WF_Tour_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: WF_Tour_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9402_Tour_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9402_Tour_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: WF_Tour_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: WF_Tour_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: WF_Tour_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: WF_Tour_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9402_Tour_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9402_Tour_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: WF_Tour_3
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: WF_Tour_3_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: WF_Tour_3_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: WF_Tour_3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9402_Tour_3_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9402_Tour_3_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: GC_Rally_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: GC_Rally_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: GC_Rally_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: GC_Rally_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_Rally_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_Rally_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: GC_Rally_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: GC_Rally_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: GC_Rally_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: GC_Rally_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_Rally_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_Rally_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: GC_Tour_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: GC_Tour_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: GC_Tour_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: GC_Tour_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_Tour_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_Tour_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: GC_Tour_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: GC_Tour_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: GC_Tour_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: GC_Tour_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_Tour_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_Tour_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: GC_Tour_3
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: GC_Tour_3_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: GC_Tour_3_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: GC_Tour_3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_Tour_3_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_Tour_3_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: BS_Rally_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: BS_Rally_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: BS_Rally_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: BS_Rally_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Rally_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9404_Rally_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: BS_Rally_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: BS_Rally_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: BS_Rally_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: BS_Rally_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Rally_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9404_Rally_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: BS_Tour_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: BS_Tour_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: BS_Tour_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: BS_Tour_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9404_Tour_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: BS_Tour_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: BS_Tour_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: BS_Tour_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: BS_Tour_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9404_Tour_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: BS_Tour_3
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: BS_Tour_3_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: BS_Tour_3_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: BS_Tour_3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_3_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9404_Tour_3_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EW_Rally_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EW_Rally_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EW_Rally_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EW_Rally_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9405_Rally_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_Rally_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EW_Rally_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EW_Rally_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EW_Rally_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EW_Rally_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9405_Rally_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Rally_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_Rally_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Rally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Rally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EW_Tour_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EW_Tour_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EW_Tour_1_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EW_Tour_1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9405_Tour_1_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_Tour_1_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EW_Tour_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EW_Tour_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EW_Tour_2_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EW_Tour_2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9405_Tour_2_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_Tour_2_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: EW_Tour_3
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: EW_Tour_3_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: EW_Tour_3_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: EW_Tour_3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9405_Tour_3_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@94_ReadRules_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_Tour_3_Proposal_2"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9401_Races
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: 9401_Races_Quest
  NpcDestinationId: 9401_Horse
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_TutorialComplete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9401_T1_5_Races_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9401_Races_title"
  Description: "@9401_EFCircuit_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_EFCircuit_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_EFCircuit_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_EFCircuit_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_EFCircuit_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9402_Races
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: 9402_Races_Quest
  NpcDestinationId: 9402_Conman
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9401_VectorWF_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9402_T2_10_Races_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9402_Races_title"
  Description: "@9402_Races_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_WFCircuit_Start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_WFCircuit_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_WFCircuit_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_WFCircuit_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9403_Races
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: 9403_Races_Quest
  NpcDestinationId: 9403_Wolf
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_FreeWolves_complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9403_T3_15_Races_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9403_Races_title"
  Description: "@9403_WolfRaces_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_WolfRaces_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_WolfRaces_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9403_WolfRaces_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9403_ValenciaIznov_02_Dialogue"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9404_Races
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: 9404_Races_Quest
  NpcDestinationId: 9404_Record
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9403_VectorBS_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9404_T4_15_Races_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Races_title"
  Description: "@9403_BSRaces_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_BSRaces_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9403_BSRaces_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9403_BSRaces_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9403_BSRaces_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 9405_Races
  Type: MountUnlock
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: 9405_Races_Quest
  NpcDestinationId: 9405_Lion
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 9405_T5_15_Races_Complete
  RequiredAchievementId: 9405_RescueLion_Complete
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: 9405_T5_15_Races_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9405_Races_title"
  Description: "@9405_LionRaces_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9405_LionRaces_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9405_LionRaces_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9405_LionRaces_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9405_LionRaces_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: MountRace_ScaleTest_1
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_6_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_Tour_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: MountRace_ScaleTest_2
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_6_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_Tour_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Short
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Short_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_6_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_Tour_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Short
  Type: MountRace
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: true
  Task: MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Short_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@9404_Tour_6_title"
  Description: "@9401_Tour_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_Tour_start"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@9401_Tour_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@9401_Tour_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@9401_Tour_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
